I'm at the cafe!
Oh!
I'm here.
We've eaten a lot.
So we're going to sit down and take a break.
It was hot.
But here, there are parasols.
It's so white and the weather is so nice.
Summer is coming.
You know, I've been into that lately.
Summer has started.
You said that before.
Yeah, that's all I do these days.
Summer has started.
Singing is my cue that summer has started.
What? I thought he was coming.
I thought that was your cue.
Oh, he's here?
Are you scared?
Summer's here. He's here.
Oh, my God. Are you kidding me? Is it?
How is that possible? That's scary. It's a song about a girl who chases after a boy.
Oh, that's a cue. Surely, the cue is down.
Yes, it is.
I'm sure I've heard it a lot.
The cue is down.
When the cue comes, it'll be at number 2 or something.
No way. No, it's not.
Oh, no? That's not good, is it?
No, no, no, no, no.
I don't always look at the lyrics like this.
I always have the image that I'm wearing solo ears even in Nikolov's songs.
I also think of Chiara Tiara's
The center of the song is
It's always me, Zoraijin.
Zoraijin, I thought I was absolute.
A very strong-willed guy.
But it's like that, isn't it?
I think there was a lyric that sounded a little Japanese.
It's gonna be alright
I thought this place was going to be another biolai someday.
What's that?
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God! Look at the gradient!
It's amazing!
Cherry blossoms here!
Oh, my gosh!
Wow! Wow!
The night sky!
I love these colors!
What? Why is it like this?
That's weird.
There's no film outside, is there?
Wow!
That's weird.
Yes, it is.
Bon appétit.
Mmm! It's so good!
It's so refreshing.
There's coco.
Nata de coco? Coco.
I've never heard of nata de coco.
We're friends. We have Coco.
It's delicious. We eat it all the time.
It's true. She eats all the time.
He sucks on it. Look at this.
Mouthfuls? Oh, yeah.
It's going my way.
I made a mistake.
Great. Okay, thanks for the food. You're going to suck it first?
Suck it.
I put it on my meat.
Oh, it's right around here.
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
It's delicious! The juices are so good.
Oh, no, I didn't get it.
Let's try it again.
I'll do it exactly the same way now.
Please do.
I'll take it.
I can't drink it.
I can't drink. Would you prefer it this way?
Yes, it would be better this way. This is better.
Wow! The juices are juicy!
Is it good?
Yes, it is! It's so good!
Bon appétit!
It's so juicy!
It's amazing.
How do you make it? For everyone.
I'm sure.
It's amazing.
Yum!
Happy day!
It's so perfect right now, isn't it?
It's just perfect to be in the shade.
But it's sunny and there's a slight cool breeze.
I mean, look at it. It's so nice.
It's like being abroad.It's like overseas.
Right?
Behind here.
I love it.
It's great.
Look.
Wow, cabbage!
Big cabbage!
It's good.
Delicious!
[Hajime Shacho's ending]
And I've been wanting to eat a small basket.
Iyori's doing a drama, right?
Yeah, yeah.
I want to do some DIY.
I want to learn something on Twitter.
I've been thinking about going to Chinatown.
To the manager.
I said, "I want to do DIY.
I said, "Well, let's do DIY today. I was like, "Oh, really?
Oh, really?
Oh, sure, I want to do it, too.
But I'm afraid of you, Kihara-chan.
Oh, I want to do it, too.
You're going to hammer nails into your fingers, aren't you?
You know, a nail...
I'm scared.
Will it stop?
But when I was little...
When you were little, even in elementary school...
It's like a shelf or something...
Yes, they make them... like in cram school...
I'm surprisingly good at cram school stuff.
What's that?
It takes time.
I thought it was scary, so I quit.
Let's do DIY sometime.
I want to.
What do you want to build?
I want to make a doghouse.
Oh, that's a good idea.
Yum! I just ate a whole loaf. I'm going to have some doughy bread later.
I'll see you later.
I'm going to eat today.
But I'll be hungry after an hour or so.
I went out for yakiniku with Keara the other night. It was delicious.
I've been wanting to go to yakiniku, and Keala said let's go eat yakiniku.
Isn't Keala cute? She's so cute!
I think her LINE was cute.
She sent me a LINE stamp saying I was cute. Like, "Why?
She was cute... on line. What?
"Do you want to go to yakiniku? And I said, "Sure," and he said, "Yay!
Yay! I wanted to go to yakiniku!
That's cute. So?
It's more than just saying, "Sure." When I think that he wanted to go too, I'm glad I invited him.
I think it's important to say something like that, so everyone should do it.
Yay! I wanted to go too! Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I really wanted to go.
I go to yakitori alone, but I don't really like yakiniku.
Yakitori.
Yakitori?
I can eat yakitori and udon by myself, but yakiniku...
I can't. It stinks.
I had beef tongue in Sendai.
I'm out! Just in time.
On the day of Rakuten Igrafes, we had a rehearsal and went back to the hotel.
We had 2 or 3 hours of free time before the game started.
There was a Riyu restaurant next to the hotel, but the meeting time was half an hour later?
I ordered right away, but I could only taste the first bite.
I took a picture of it. Suddenly...
Then I was like, "Oh no, it's going to be 50 minutes already! Like that.
And you wrote a post in 5 minutes. You didn't enjoy it!
I wanted to eat beef tongue in Sendai.
I'm glad you got it done. I bet your manager was all over you.
Everyone was buzzing. Everyone was here.
So, what? You really went, Kiara? It was like...
That's amazing how dynamic she is.
I'm starting to like Pink Grape.
You did it!
You don't have any likes or dislikes, so that's great.
But okra... okra and fava beans are the only things I can't get over.
Okra and fava beans?
I hate fava beans just from the memory.
Why not? What happened?
I was in a class in elementary school where we were required to eat everything.
Oh, yeah.
And I've been eating them all my life, ever since I was an adult.
I've eaten six copies of every book I've ever read in my entire adult life, and fava beans? It was the first fava beans in your life.
I liked eza beans.
But when I tried them, they were so bad.
I didn't like them.
Yeah, I had to eat them all.
Even during recess.
Oh, what? I had one too, in the first grade.
Me and another boy.
He and I ate really late.
We ate until lunch break.
The dishes were already taken care of.
I'll bring it to the lunchroom myself.
That's right, that's right, that's right, that's right.Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, you bring your own.
It's soooo good!
Krastal.
Then I'll eat it.
It's sponge cake.
I've never had Taiwanese sponge cake.
It's fluffy!
It's fluffy.
Oh, no!
It's so yellow!
Most sponge cakes smell yellow.
I like the yellow color.
It smells so sweet.
It's not tarnished.
I forgot something.
We had a kanji test.
My teacher's name was Hashi.
It's a bridge.
Hashi was on the test.
I think I was missing a mouthful.
You see that one?
The one on the left under the right one on the right
That's mine too, right?
I think I was missing that one.
At that time, the doctor said...
I have a lot of mouths because I talk too much.
So...
Wow.
But that's how you remember it.
That's how I remember it.
And I remember it so well.
That's a mysterious story.
Yum!
It's good, isn't it?
It tastes just like that.
Egg bowl.
It's good.
Just a little bit.
Don't insure it.
My elementary school was like a dojo.
You get stamps for saying fast words to the teacher and solving math problems.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's what everyone does.
Do you get something if you get a stamp?
I don't know. I didn't do it.
You didn't do it.
I didn't do it.
I'm pretty sure that if I did something like that.
I want to get more stamps than other people.
You'll do it, won't you, Keira?
You're losing too much in the weirdest places, aren't you?
I still get stamps when I get them.
If you want to collect stamps, you can do a lot of things, can't you?
Let's go to the lesson place first.
Then we can get stamps.
That's great.
I'll make you a stamp book.
You'll make me a stamp book?
And when I get enough, we'll go out for barbecue.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's good.
Let's do it.
If you're late, they'll take one stamp away from you.
But it could be negative.
It's like this.
Oh, yeah, sorry.
Here, Chip.
You said you always do it last night.
I'm always trying to put the kibosh on things.
You know, I wrote an Insta?
I'm going to work on my nails now, remember?
Yeah, that's what I always say.
You know, people's comments.
I need a good shape, and good luck with my nails.
You're always saying that.
Give it back. I'll try my best to sleep.
I'll try my best to sleep. Give it back.
I'm sorry, but I did my best to clean up.
I'll keep it simple like you, Mayuka.
Keep it simple.
I'm really full.
You're so full.
We ate a lot, didn't we?
The first batch of steamed buns.
That was a lot of food for one person.
And then I drank tapioca.
And a second glass of juice.
I'll have some Mosaic, too.
I'd like that.
I don't know. I don't know.
It's black.
They say it rings a bell.
You're...
Dumb.
The way he shows it
They say it can ring this bell.
The sound purifies me.
I want to make a big sound.
Go ahead, Chiara!
Okay, I'm full now.Yes, I'm full now.
I think we're going to go and get our fortunes told.
But before we do, I'd like to ring this in.
See you soon.
Thank you for watching.
This way.
Here we go.
Wait for me.
Practice.
How's it coming?
Oh, my God, it's coming out... right here.
Like this.
Here we go.
Give it a ring.
That's it.
Ready?
Wow.
It's so good.
It was bigger than I thought it would be.
What?
Oh, that's it. That's it.
I'm so surprised.
It was bigger than I thought.
Wow.
That was a surprise.
I'm allowed to ring this. You scared me, it was bigger than I thought.
And the other day I was afraid to ring it. Why?
Why? It didn't ring that high. Don't worry, I heard mine.
It's like a marshmallow. It's definitely a marshmallow.
Here we go. - Okay, I'm going. I'm going? You can go.
Ready? Yes. This is it, right? Yeah. - Okay.
I'm going. Okay.
Oh, my God.
You scared me.
I'm always surprised when I know what I'm doing.
It sounded good.
Yes!
I'm here for my reading. I'm here.
I'd like to have our fortunes read. I'm very nervous.
I'm very nervous. I've never had my name read before.
I'm looking forward to it.
We'll combine your birthday and palm readings for your happiness.
What makes you happy? What is the secret? I'll tell you.
You two are complete opposites.
Heh...
You really have opposite roles.
Heh.
So in a way, I'm giving you the opposite.
But what makes them unique and what they exhibit is different.
Then you two are the same woman.
That's where we're going to be.
If this one is for fall, this one is for spring.
So, the two of you, you know, what kind of a combination...
What she can do, she can do.
What this lady can do, she can't do.
What this one can do, she can't do.
So, the two of you can make up for each other.
If you think of them as two people who make up for what you can't do, it's a very good balance.
You're probably right. And here is the star of popularity for both of you.
You give people attention, you give people customers, and you don't buy them a drink.
I will have people say, "That's very nice, isn't it?
And then she says, you know, in that sense, I'm very good at living a life that is related to people.
As a star, she can't work hard at something she doesn't like to do.
Maybe!
As a person, I ask myself the question, "Are you doing what you really want to do? I think it's hard to do what you really want to do when you are so passionate about it,
It's the same with athletes. Even if you become an athlete because you love running, there are still hardships.
But they go back to the way they were or they go back to saying they love to run.
It is very good to have something like that.
So, let's see which of you ladies would like to start first.
Well, let's start with me.
She's very proactive.
That's great.
She's very clear.
The performance line is thin, but..,
It's growing nicely.
No health problems.
And the other thing about her is that she's
from the performance line.
It's a ponce.
It's true.
It's both ways.
Amazing.
Maybe it means they want to make money. Financially secure.
Not a girl who wants to work in a company, but a girl who wants to be independent.
That kind of career woman, that's what I'm looking for,
So you can be honest about this.
Yes, thank you very much. You've done a great job.
Both of them are in it very well.
Yes, you'll make a lot of money. You did it.
And over here, people are nice, kind, gentle, considerate young lady.
And here they are attached, and there's a difference in the bottom.
This one here is an artist.
It's pretty much the opposite. This one, too.
So here, too, we do what we can't do, and we do it with each other.
The nature of taking each other's work is perfect for working together.The nature of taking each other's work is perfect for working together.
Yes, thank you.
Please make the most of this difference.
Yes, I'm glad.
Is everything all right?
Yes, thank you.
Thank you very much.
I did it the other way around, but I thought it would be nice if we could support each other. You're right, but I don't see Kiara down a lot, and I don't want to show it.
I'm fine with showing it to her, but I don't want to show it to her, and I don't want to show it to you, but maybe we both do.
I'm always like a koala, a koala to Kiara, a koala to Kiara.
I've always been energized by koala to koala, and I want to continue to do so in the future.
After this, we ate a lot of food, and then we want to go back home.
I hope everyone had a good time!
Do you like kia mai?
Yes. Bye.
Bye, bye, bye.
Bye bye.